Guide to the Lloyd R. Simons Director of Extension papers, 1932-1935.
Simons, Lloyd R., Director of Extension papers, 1932-1935.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Lloyd R. Simons Director of Extension papers, 1932-1935.
21-24-108
L. R. Simons
7.5 cubic ft.
Correspondence, photographs, publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, scrapbooks, photoprints, publications, and other records of the Director of Extension of the New York State College of Agriculture at Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, scrapbooks, photoprints, publications, and other records of the Director of Extension of the New York State College of Agriculture at Cornell University.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Simons, L. R.; New York State College of Agriculture.
Subjects:
Agricultural extension work -- New York (State); University extension -- New York (State)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Department of Agriculture and Miscellaneous, Washington, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
- Secretary of Agriculture -H.A. Wallace; R.G.Tugwell, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Secretary of Agriculture - Arthur Hyde, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Bureau of Entomology - C.L. Marlatt, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Food and Drug Administration - W.G. Campbell, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Bureau of Plant Industry, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Secretary of Commerce, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Office of Cooperative Marketing, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Federal Farm Board - Henry Morgenthau, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 11-12)
- United States Farm Relief Bill, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Office of Experimental Stations - J.T. Jardine, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- United States Treasury and Post Office Bill - Austin Amendment, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 15-16)
- Governor Herbert H. Lehman, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Governor Franklin D. Roosevelt, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Conservation Commission - Osborne; Gaston; Morgenthau, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 19-20)
- Agriculture and Markets (Miscellaneous), 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Architect, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Department of Public Sorks, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Budget Director - Mark Graves, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Comptroller, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Harlan H. Horner, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 26-27)
- Education Department, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Department of Health, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Public Service Commission - M. C. Burritt, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Extension, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Extension Director, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Central Farm Bureau Office - Flansburgh; Kelsey; Morris, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 33-34)
- Junior Extension - Wright; Hoefer, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Robinson, Montgomery, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- C.A. Taylor, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Extension - Home Made Farm Relief, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 38-39)
- Farm and Home Week, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 40-41)
- Faculty - Agricultural, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Faculty - University, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Faculty - Home Economics, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Farm Practice, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Floriculture, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 46-47)
- Forestry, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Graduate School, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Heads of Departments and Offices, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Home Economics - Flora Rose, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 51-53)
- H.B. Meek; F.H. Randolph, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Information Service - Bristow Adams, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 55-56)
- Law College, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Library - College, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Library - University, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Meteorology, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Music Department, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Physical Education, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Plant Breeding, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Plant Pathology - Guterman, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 7-8)
- Spray Residue Correspondence, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Pomology, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Poultry Husbandry - James Rice, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 11-12)
- President's Office, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Provost - A.R. Mann, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 14-15)
- L.C. Boochever, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Purchasing Office, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Supplies, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 18-20)
- Director of Admissions, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Rural Education - R.M. Stewart, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Rural Social Organization - Dwight Sanderson, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Secretary, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Cornelius Betten, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- A.W. Gibson, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Secretary - University, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Treasurer, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- R.H. Wheeler, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Cornell University Christian Association, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Vegetable Crops, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Veterinary, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- County Agents - Albany, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- County Agents - Allegheny, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- County Agents - Broome, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- County Agents - Cattaraugus, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- County Agents - Cayuga, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- County Agents - Chautauqua, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- County Agents - Chemung, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- County Agents - Chenango, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- County Agents - Clinton, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- County Agents - Columbia, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- County Agents - Cortland, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- County Agents - Delaware, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- County Agents - Dutchess, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- County Agents - Erie, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- County Agents - Essex, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- County Agents - Franklin, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- County Agents - Fulton, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- County Agents - Genesee, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- County Agents - Greene, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- County Agents - Herkimer, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- County Agents - Jefferson, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- County Agents - Livingston, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- County Agents - Madison, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- County Agents - Monroe, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- County Agents - Montgomery, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- County Agents - Nassau, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- County Agents - Niagara, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- County Agents - Oneida, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- County Agents - Onondaga, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- County Agents - Ontario, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- County Agents - Orange, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- County Agents - Orleans, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- County Agents - Oswego, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- County Agents - Otsego, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- County Agents - Rensselaer, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- County Agents - Rockland, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- County Agents - St. Lawrence, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- County Agents - Saratoga, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- County Agents - Schenectady, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- County Agents - Schoharie, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 72)
- County Agents - Schuyler, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 73)
- County Agents - Seneca, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 74)
- County Agents - Steuben, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 75)
- County Agents - Suffolk, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 76)
- County Agents - Sullivan, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 77)
- County Agents - Tioga, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 78)
- County Agents - Tompkins, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 79)
- County Agents - Ulster, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 80)
- County Agents - Warren, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 81)
- County Agents - Washington, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 82)
- County Agents - Wayne, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 83)
- County Agents - Westchester, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 84)
- County Agents - Wyoming, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 85)
- Simons, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 86)
- Gibson - Orientation, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 87)
- Cornelius Betten, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 88)
- R.H. Wheeler, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 89)
- College of Veterinary Science, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 90)
- Montgomery Robinson, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 91)
- C.A. Taylor, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 92)
- C.A. Taylor - Radio, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 93)
- E A. Bates, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Expense Accounts - V.B. Hart, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Bristow Adams, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- George Butts, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- E. A. Flansburgh, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- F. B. Morris, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Leo Muckle, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- W. J. Wright, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Albert Hoefer, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Mrs Ruby Green Smith, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Bess McDermand, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Caroline Morton, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Martha Eddy, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Dorothy Delany, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Agricultural Economics, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Agricultural Engineering, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 16-17)
- Agronomy, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Animal Husbandry, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Dairy Industry, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Entomology, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Forestry, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Plant Breeding, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Plant Pathology, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Pomology, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Poultry, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Rural Education, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Rural Social Organization, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Vegetable Crops, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Flora Rose, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- College of Home Economics, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- A, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- American Agriculturist, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- American Bankers' Association, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- American Farm Bureau Federation - E. A. O'Neal, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- B, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- H. E. Babcock, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- M. C. Bond, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 38-39)
- C, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- D, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Dairymen's League, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- E, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Epsilon Sigma Phi, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- F, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Federal Land Bank - Springfield, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- G, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- G.L.F. Exchange, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Good Seed Company, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Grange - National, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- H, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- V. B. Hart, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Hotels, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- I-L, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Land Grant Association, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- M, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- N, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- New York Seed Improvement Cooperative Association, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- New York State Bankers Association, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- New York State Department of Agriculture and Markets - Webster Birdsall, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- New York State Education Department, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- New York State Farm Bureau Federation - E. S. Foster, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- New York State Federation of Home Bureaus, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- New York State Library Association, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- O-P, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- James Pringle - Grange, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- R, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 67)
- S, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- Sheffield Producers Cooperative Association, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 69)
- T, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- U-W, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- G. F. Warren, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 72)
- Cooperative Extension - Singleton; Graham; Dixon, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- M. Thayer, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- H. W. Hodhbaum, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- C. W. Warburton - Director of Extension, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- C. B. Smith, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Annual Federal Report, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Salary and Leave Certificates, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Albany, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Allegheny, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Broome, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Cattaraugus, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Cayuga, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Chautauqua, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Chemung, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Chenango, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Clinton, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Columbia, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Delaware, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Dutchess, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Erie, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Essex, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Franklin, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Fulton, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Genesee, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Greene, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Herkimer, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Jefferson, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Livingston, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Madison, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Monroe, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Montgomery, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Nassau, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Niagara, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Oneida, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Onondaga, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Ontario, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Orange, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Orleans, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Oswego, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Otsego, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Rensselaer, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- St. Lawrence, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Saratoga, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Schenectady, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Schoharie, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Seneca, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Steuben, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Suffolk, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Sullivan, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Tioga, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Tompkins, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Ulster, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Warren, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Washington, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Wayne, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Westchester, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Wyoming, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- Removal of Old Orchards, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- Rural Rehabilitation Agents and Committees - W. Georgia, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Rural Youth Problem, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- Report on Winter Injury to Orchards, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 61)
- Soil Erosion, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 62)
- Speeches, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 63)
- State Fair - 1934, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 64)
- Nathan Straus Reports, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 65)
- Budget for Rural Rehabilitation, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 66)
- Corporation Meeting, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 67)
- Rural Rehabilitation Corporation - C. Carpenter; W. Georgia, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 68)
- Rural Rehabilitation - W. Georgia; County Agricultural Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 69-74)
- T.E.R.A. - J. Strahan; W. Georgia, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 75-76)
- T.E.R.A. - Potato Project, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 77-78)
- Tompkins County Development Board - Joseph Myers, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 79-80)
- Rural Electrification Project - T.E.R.A., 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 81-83)
- Agricultural Aerial Survey - F. Belmer, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- American Institute of Cooperation, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Bang's Disease, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Bean Marketing Agreement, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Boy Scouts of America, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Conference State Schools of Agriculture, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Agricultural Advisory Committee on Rural Rehabilitation (T.E.R.A.), 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 7-9)
- Agricultural Conference Committees, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Committee on Professional Improvement, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 11-12)
- Discussion Groups, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Dutch Elm Disease, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Emergency Drought Crops - John Barron; County Agricultural Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 15-18)
- Emergency Feed Loans, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Farm and Home Week - 1935, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Farmers' Tax Problem, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Foreign Agricultural Extension Activities, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- G.L.F. - Fertilizers, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Hay - F. Henry; C. Warburton; County Agricultural Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 24-26)
- Hay Certificates, Rules and Regulations, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Key Bankers - 1935, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Land Grant Colleges Association, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Land Grant College Bill - Willard Munson; E. Foster, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Governor Lehman's Advisory Commission, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Master Farmers, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Mastitis, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Milk Publicity Campaign, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Milk Research Council, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Miscellaneous, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- National Association of County Agricultural Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- National Associaton of Marketing Officials, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- National Commercial and Breeder Hatchery Coordinating Committee, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- National Cooperative Council, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- National Fur Tax Committee, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Northeastern Regional Conference - New York, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Northeastern Agricultural Conferencee - H. Baker, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 44-49)
- Northeastern Dairy Conference, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Northeastern Poultry Producers' Council, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Northeastern Regional Conference - February, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Orchard Rehabilitation Loans, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Annual Outlook Conference, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Agriculture Outlook and Dairy Situation - 1935, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Periods of Service, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Changes in Personnel, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Professional Improvement Group, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Livingston Farrand (President, Cornell University), 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- A. Mann (Provost), 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 60)
- C. Ladd (Dean), 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 61)
- L. Simons, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- A. Gibson, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- R. Wheeler, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Cornelius Betten, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 65)
- Business Office, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 66)
- Appointments and Resignations (Counties), 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 67-68)
- Circular Letters (Extension), 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 69)
- Montgomery Robinson, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 1-3)
- C. Taylor (Radio), 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- E. Bates (Indian Extension), 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Bristow Adams (Publications), 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- A, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- E. Flansburgh, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- L. Kelsey, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- F. Morris, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- L. Muckle, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- W. Wright, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Albert Hoefer, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Dorothy Delany, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- F. Heinzelman, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Mrs Ruby Green Smith, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Caroline Morton, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Mrs Martha Eddy, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Agricultural Economics, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Agricultural Engineering, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Agronomy, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Animal Husbandry, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Dairy Industry, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Entomology, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Floriculture, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Forestry, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Plant Breeding, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Plant Pathology, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Pomology, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Poultry, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Rural Education, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Rural Social Organization, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Vegetable Crops, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Flora Rose, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- College of Home Economics, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Albany County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Allegheny County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Broome County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Cattaraugus County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Cayuga County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Chautauqua County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Chemung County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Chenango County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Clinton County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Columbia County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Cortland County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Delaware County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Dutchess County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Erie County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Essex County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Franklin County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Fulton County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Genesee County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Greene County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Herkimer County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Jefferson County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Lewis County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Livingston County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Madison County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Monroe County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 60)
- Montgomery County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Nassau County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 62)
- Niagara County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 63)
- Oneida County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 64)
- Onondaga County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 65)
- Ontario County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 66)
- Orange County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 67)
- Orleans County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 68)
- Oswego County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 69)
- Otsego County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 70)
- Rensselaer County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 71)
- Rockland County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 72)
- St. Lawrence County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 73)
- Saratoga County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 74)
- Schenectady County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 75)
- Schoharie County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 76)
- Schuyler County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 77)
- Seneca County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 78)
- Steuben County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 79)
- Suffolk County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 80)
- Sullivan County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 81)
- Tioga County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 82)
- Tompkins County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 83)
- Ulster County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 84)
- Warren County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 85)
- Washington County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 86)
- Wayne County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 87)
- Westchester County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 88)
- Wyoming County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 89)
- Yates County Agents, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 90)
- Agricultural Experiment Station, Geneva, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 91)
- American Agriculturist, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 92)
- American Bankers' Association - Dan Otis, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 93)
- American Farm Bureau Federation - Edward O'Neal; W. Ogg, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 94-96)
- American Farm Bureau Federation Newsletter, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 97)
- B, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 98)
- H. Babcock, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 99)
- M. Bond, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 100)
- C, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- D, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 2)